let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "question": "She updated her _______ to apply for the job.",
    "answer": "resume",
    "options": [
      "interview",
      "achievement",
      "resume",
      "associate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "question": "The _______ for the position was announced yesterday.",
    "answer": "opening",
    "options": [
      "confidence",
      "hire",
      "opening",
      "managerial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "question": "The _______ submitted their application online.",
    "answer": "applicant",
    "options": [
      "reference",
      "certification",
      "applicant",
      "condition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "question": "The job _______ includes a bachelor's degree.",
    "answer": "requirement",
    "options": [
      "requirement",
      "payroll",
      "hire",
      "proficiency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "question": "He worked hard to _______ the deadline.",
    "answer": "meet",
    "options": [
      "recruit",
      "meet",
      "appeal",
      "specialize"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "question": "The company is looking for a/an _______ individual.",
    "answer": "qualified",
    "options": [
      "apprehensive",
      "training",
      "associate",
      "qualified"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "question": "The _______'s interview went well.",
    "answer": "candidate",
    "options": [
      "candidate",
      "condition",
      "certification",
      "appeal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "question": "She spoke with _______ during the presentation.",
    "answer": "confidence",
    "options": [
      "confidence",
      "proficiency",
      "managerial",
      "lack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "question": "The team was impressed by his _______ developed skills.",
    "answer": "highly",
    "options": [
      "highly",
      "entitle",
      "applicant",
      "associate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "question": "He displayed a highly _______ attitude during the interview.",
    "answer": "professional",
    "options": [
      "lack",
      "applicant",
      "employment",
      "professional"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 11,
    "question": "She prepared thoroughly for the _______.",
    "answer": "interview",
    "options": [
      "hire",
      "eligible",
      "managerial",
      "interview"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 12,
    "question": "The company decided to _______ him after the second round.",
    "answer": "hire",
    "options": [
      "lack",
      "eligible",
      "hire",
      "candidate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 13,
    "question": "The new employees will undergo _______ next week.",
    "answer": "training",
    "options": [
      "achievement",
      "managerial",
      "training",
      "resume"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 14,
    "question": "They contacted his previous employer for a _______.",
    "answer": "reference",
    "options": [
      "diligent",
      "reference",
      "interview",
      "lack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 15,
    "question": "The open _______ requires strong communication skills.",
    "answer": "position",
    "options": [
      "position",
      "condition",
      "certification",
      "payroll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 16,
    "question": "His academic _______ stood out on his resume.",
    "answer": "achievement",
    "options": [
      "candidate",
      "occupation",
      "applicant",
      "achievement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 17,
    "question": "The panel was genuinely _______ by her presentation.",
    "answer": "impressed",
    "options": [
      "familiar",
      "impressed",
      "associate",
      "resume"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 18,
    "question": "She received a/an _______ performance review.",
    "answer": "excellent",
    "options": [
      "excellent",
      "apprehensive",
      "lack",
      "entitle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 19,
    "question": "He is _______ for the leadership program.",
    "answer": "eligible",
    "options": [
      "eligible",
      "highly",
      "wage",
      "managerial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 20,
    "question": "It's important to _______ the key strengths of each team member.",
    "answer": "identify",
    "options": [
      "identify",
      "employment",
      "associate",
      "confidence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 21,
    "question": "She is a/an _______ at the law firm.",
    "answer": "associate",
    "options": [
      "employment",
      "associate",
      "condition",
      "recruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 22,
    "question": "The car is in excellent _______ after the recent maintenance.",
    "answer": "condition",
    "options": [
      "condition",
      "employment",
      "proficiency",
      "certification"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 23,
    "question": "She is actively seeking _______ after completing her degree.",
    "answer": "employment",
    "options": [
      "resume",
      "wage",
      "employment",
      "entitle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 24,
    "question": "The _______ of experience hindered his job search.",
    "answer": "lack",
    "options": [
      "lack",
      "degree",
      "payroll",
      "appeal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 25,
    "question": "Her _______ skills have greatly contributed to the team's success.",
    "answer": "managerial",
    "options": [
      "confidence",
      "apprehensive",
      "lack",
      "managerial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 26,
    "question": "He is known for being _______ in his work.",
    "answer": "diligent",
    "options": [
      "applicant",
      "diligent",
      "apprehensive",
      "wage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 27,
    "question": "She's _______ with the latest industry trends.",
    "answer": "familiar",
    "options": [
      "entitled",
      "familiar",
      "conditioned",
      "diligent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 28,
    "question": "His _______ in programming languages is impressive.",
    "answer": "proficiency",
    "options": [
      "prospective",
      "payroll",
      "proficiency",
      "employment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 29,
    "question": "The _______ employee had an impressive resume.",
    "answer": "prospective",
    "options": [
      "prospective",
      "associate",
      "apprehensive",
      "familiar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 30,
    "question": "The product's unique features and design _______ to consumers.",
    "answer": "appeal",
    "options": [
      "appeal",
      "recruit",
      "entitle",
      "hire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 31,
    "question": "They _______ in digital marketing strategies.",
    "answer": "specialize",
    "options": [
      "specialize",
      "associate",
      "recruit",
      "manage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 32,
    "question": "She felt _______ about the upcoming interview.",
    "answer": "apprehensive",
    "options": [
      "lack",
      "apprehensive",
      "confidence",
      "certification"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 33,
    "question": "They hired a/an _______ to improve efficiency.",
    "answer": "consultant",
    "options": [
      "applicant",
      "consultant",
      "certification",
      "candidate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 34,
    "question": "Meeting certain criteria will _______ you to benefits.",
    "answer": "entitle",
    "options": [
      "position",
      "specialize",
      "entitle",
      "familiarize"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 35,
    "question": "He earned a _______ in computer science.",
    "answer": "degree",
    "options": [
      "wage",
      "payroll",
      "degree",
      "reference"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 36,
    "question": "She manages the company's _______ system.",
    "answer": "payroll",
    "options": [
      "lack",
      "specialize",
      "impressed",
      "payroll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 37,
    "question": "The HR department will _______ new employees next month.",
    "answer": "recruit",
    "options": [
      "recruit",
      "specialize",
      "resume",
      "associate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 38,
    "question": "She received her _______ in project management.",
    "answer": "certification",
    "options": [
      "consultant",
      "certification",
      "requirement",
      "appeal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 39,
    "question": "His _______ as a firefighter requires bravery and quick thinking in emergency situations.",
    "answer": "occupation",
    "options": [
      "managerial",
      "occupation",
      "requirement",
      "recruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 40,
    "question": "They negotiated a higher _______ for the employees.",
    "answer": "wage",
    "options": [
      "payroll",
      "wage",
      "degree",
      "employment"
    ]
  }
];

